The courage to love again...
Safe Harbour is a drama, romance film directed by Bill Corcoran.
Melissa Gilbert stars in this film adaptation of Danielle Steel's bestselling novel, in which a young girl named Pip and her mother meet an artist
on the beach in Safe Harbour, where they have retreated in order to recover from the devastating loss of Pip's father and brother.
Ophelia MacKenzie, played by Melissa Gilbert.
Matt Bowles, played by Brad Johnson.
Philippa 'Pip' MacKenzie, played by Liana Liberato.
Andrea Wilson, played by Rebecca Staab.
Bob, played by Michael DeLorenzo.
Jeff, played by Michael Jace.
Safe Harbour (also known as Danielle Steel's Safe Harbour) is a 2007 American direct-to-video romantic drama
film directed by Bill Corcoran, based upon the 2003 novel of the same name by Danielle Steel.
The film explores themes of jealousy, based on novel
or book, serial killer, embezzlement.
The tone is emotional.